Hello friends, hello to all of you,
welcome once again and in today's video,
friends, in today's video, we will tell you
how to start a policy from ICICI Lombard online through agent photo.
So friends, first of all, we start by
opening our Google Play
and entering our IAS added toe ID and password.
We login to it. I have logged in to my video.
After logging in,
we will show you the effect of bike, four
wheeler, private vehicle. You will see the effect of your
two wheeler and you have to do it.
When you might get out, you have to do Dr., then I
refuse and from Hindu editing and
labs, admin number from Mithun point, I had hit someone else
before and the hot is broken, so we are
insuring it. That is for you, friend, I have
totally shot it. It is a nice
city name part, so we used to fast it.
Advice of good
that click on it. After this, it will ask first of all,
now we enter one more thing, number,
whatever it is on the bike car number, we
enter it.
You have to click on New Delhi,
click on cat middleten  Let's do this, if
my saree comes out, then
I hope it is okay in Vital, then
this is a little problem, in this my Activa 4G, I have to
confirm that it
basically does 4G and all this is
normal, I have picked up Haryana, which model is it,
when did I pay this bribe and after that it will be shown
that the serviceman will start using the
gate, then I showed that 1781,
one of my introductions came,
what all will be covered in it and damage
protest, my third party will be available, it is
written in the CT
and after that I will get some rights in the middle,
you will get the website, it will be a little
expensive, after that getting the product done, it will be a
little more expensive,
so here I will show you everything in
detail,
whose tips are installed in it, the decision of the same is of
382 third party, 752 and speakers
are installed of 376 and if you want to add it on the stage at the same time, then
boil off your Muktlif,
yes brother, after clicking note, you have to
enter your engine number in it, now
see that your mic is off in sight  Yes,
you refuse, I have entered the number, I have entered it,
after entering it I will ask if there is a
loan on your car, if not, take it, otherwise I will
click on it, some hyper call it
loan, enter the name of that company, there are
people with this too and there is an inch mark, if
I have to take any loan on my car, then mix it,
after that if there is any other name in
whose name you are doing insurance, then you have to
enter it, after seeing it you
tell its name, I have entered it
and after that it will ask for mobile number, what is the
fault, Kapil is doing it immediately, you
can send your number, I enter it in it,
later it will ask for email ID, email
ID and we enter the option, then I have the
prayer that if there is any
fear later, then
enter which one of your addresses, your 11th
is updated so that there is no problem, do it
and after that I will enter the pin code,
Lota, Bigg Boss will be over soon and you have to do it
in the price, just click on it
and after that
how will you make this 1781 payment today  If you do this adventure, if you do
debit card UPI send
family mixer to your customer, then
we will do UPSC interview on
Friday which was dismissed,
increase payment through advertisement, this is the phone, we
do all the payment only through men, I am
in Jabalpur, I scanned the Mughal on the phone
and will make the payment from here,
I know that at
this time there is a time, it is
necessary to make the payment within 15 minutes, brother, it is
also for the dynasty, so pay a
little attention while making the payment, it is very important to pay attention, if you are doing
any other work,
stop it, do
not check the internet at all because the
company sends the points a little late, for
this you have to enter the mail,
you have to talk comfortably, then that is
its pole Singh Anil, so let's see,
my payment has been successful from me, you have received
that compound policy here, this is what
Congress Muslims
spoon school transformer, this proposal number is
this, can leave policy online part
dashboard, you can download your points from here
- if we
talk then Math - opposed the
That he must have become a hero, right? Let's click on this sequence,
which opposite,
put some date there quickly, after that the
police came, as soon as the policy is shifted in the name of Subhash Chandra, the
video will be available on play
and after printing it, we give it to our customer
and take our payment from him,
see friends, this work is done very quickly, there
is a great free online system inside it, if you also want to become a judge by joining us,
want to work and destroy, then you can
contact us on this number, we
can make you earn a good amount of money like Bhushan Kumar, if you have been
looted, we will loot you and you
can earn your money by eating food, so friends,
thank you very much for watching the video, if
you liked the video then definitely like, share and
subscribe.